#### Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/aashish-mamgain-a9462a103 (LinkedIn)

### Top Skills

C++

Python

Web Development

### Languages

Spanish (Elementary)
Hindi (Native or Bilingual)
English (Professional Working)

### **Publications**

Guidance to data mining in python

# **Aashish Mamgain**

Python | Machine learning

North West Delhi, Delhi, India

## Summary

Experienced Data Scientist with a demonstrated history of working in the information technology and services industry. Skilled in Python (Programming Language), Machine Learning, Data Analysis, and Django. Strong engineering professional with a Bachelor of Technology - BTech focused in Computer Science and Engineering.

## Experience

Blackcoffer
Data Scientist intern
May 2019 - October 2019 (6 months)
New Delhi Area, India

IIT kanpur Web Developer intern June 2018 - July 2018 (2 months) Kanpur

## Education

HMR Institute Of Technology And Management
Bachelor of Technology - BTech, Computer Science and
Engineering · (2015 - 2019)

Kulachi Hansraj Model School Non medical · (2003 - 2015)